{
    "question": "What is the deduced type of 'param' inside the function f() when f() is called ?",
    "code": "template<typename T> \nvoid f(T&& param); \nint value = 5; \nf(value);",
    "a": "int&",
    "b": "const int&",
    "c": "int&&",
    "d": "int",
    "answer": "a"
},
{
    "question": "What is the deduced type of 'param' inside the function f() when f() is called ?",
    "code": "template<typename T> \nvoid f(T&& param); \nconst int value = 5; \nf(value);",
    "a": "int&",
    "b": "const int&",
    "c": "int&&",
    "d": "int",
    "answer": "b"
},
{
    "question": "What is the deduced type of 'param' inside the function f() when f() is called ?",
    "code": "template<typename T> \nvoid f(T&& param); \nint value = 5; \nint& ref = value; \nf(ref);",
    "a": "int&",
    "b": "const int&",
    "c": "int&&",
    "d": "int",
    "answer": "a"
},
{
    "question": "What is the deduced type of 'param' inside the function f() when f() is called ?",
    "code": "template<typename T> \nvoid f(T&& param); \nint value = 5; \nconst int& ref = value; \nf(ref);",
    "a": "int&",
    "b": "const int&",
    "c": "int&&",
    "d": "int",
    "answer": "b"
},
{
    "question": "What is the deduced type of 'param' inside the function f() when f() is called ?",
    "code": "template<typename T> \nvoid f(T&& param); \nf(10);",
    "a": "int&",
    "b": "const int&",
    "c": "int&&",
    "d": "int",
    "answer": "c"
},
{
    "question": "What is the deduced type of T inside the function f() when f() is called ?",
    "code": "template<typename T> \nvoid f(T&& param); \nint value = 5; \nf(value);",
    "a": "int&",
    "b": "const int&",
    "c": "int&&",
    "d": "int",
    "answer": "a"
},
{
    "question": "What is the deduced type of T inside the function f() when f() is called ?",
    "code": "template<typename T> \nvoid f(T&& param); \nconst int value = 5; \nf(value);",
    "a": "int&",
    "b": "const int&",
    "c": "int&&",
    "d": "int",
    "answer": "b"
},
{
    "question": "What is the deduced type of T inside the function f() when f() is called ?",
    "code": "template<typename T> \nvoid f(T&& param); \nint value = 5; \nint& reference = value; \nf(reference);",
    "a": "int&",
    "b": "const int&",
    "c": "int&&",
    "d": "int",
    "answer": "a"
},
{
    "question": "What is the deduced type of T inside the function f() when f() is called ?",
    "code": "template<typename T> \nvoid f(T&& param); \nint value = 5; \nconst int& reference = value; \nf(reference);",
    "a": "int&",
    "b": "const int&",
    "c": "int&&",
    "d": "int",
    "answer": "b"
},
{
    "question": "What is the deduced type of T inside the function f() when f() is called ?",
    "code": "template<typename T> \nvoid f(T&& param); \nf(10);",
    "a": "int&",
    "b": "const int&",
    "c": "int&&",
    "d": "int",
    "answer": "d"
}
